# ROTEM PATRAKEEV

FRONTEND DEVELOPER \$\scrick\$ 054-4594273

# • DETAILS •

054-4594273 rotem8y@gmail.com

#### • SKILLS •

Typescript, Javascript, ES6, HTML, CSS, SASS, SCSS

React, NextJS, Vue

Webpack, Redux

jQuery, Bootstrap

Git

Node.js, Express, Puppeteer MongoDB, MySQL, SQL server Jest, Storybook

## • LINKS •

**Portfolio** 

LinkedIn

## PROFILE

I have three years of experience as a frontend developer, specializing in creating user-friendly interfaces. I'm up-to-date with the latest tech trends and eager to contribute to a dynamic team. Looking for roles that will allow me to grow my skills and have a meaningful impact on product development.

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Frontend developer at Karma Shopping

2022 - 2023

Karma is a free shopping assistant that helps you save time and money when shopping online.

- Developed UI and new features for both frontend and browser extension utilizing React, Redux, and atomic architecture principles.
- Contributed to development of a UI component library using React, Typescript, leveraging the power of Storybook for isolated component development and testing.
- Configured Webpack build pipelines for extensions.

React, Redux, ES6, Typescript, Rollup, Webpack, Storybook, Extensions API

## Frontend developer at YIT - Yedioth Information Technology

2021 - 2022

- Designed and developed responsive web applications, employing React and Typescript.
- Took full ownership of Ctech website, finishing project in 3 months using React and Typescript.
- Contributed to high-profile projects including Ynet and Vesty.
- Built CI pipelines for frontend applications deployment.

React, Typescript, Redux

## Fullstack developer at AdWorks LTD

2020 - 2021

I was responsible for executing different type of projects:

- Created a comprehensive e-commerce application using Next.js
- Developed and deployed scraping service, utilizing Node.js and Puppetter
- Developed a chrome extension.

Next.js, React, Nodej.js, Puppeteer, Chrome extension

# Web Content Editor at N & J food equipment LTD

2015 - 2019

I was responsible for the maintaining company's website, providing technical and customer support.

- Edited website content, that required knowledge of HTML, CSS
- Created tracking and analytics flows, using Google Ads and Google Analytics.
- · Created and managed campaigns in Google Ads.

# Army service

2010 - 2012

Computers Corps Commander and instructor of encryption courses.

# EDUCATION

FullStack web development course, Coding Academy (Mister bit bootcamp) 2020

Learned React, Redux, Node.js, Vue, Express project development.

B.Sc. Technology Management - Information Systems Management and Development, Holon Institute of Technology (HIT)

2015 — 2019